(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Crazyになるほど 恋している ZOMBIE
Crazy Zombie in Love
Oh, oh, oh... Zombie zombie...
HOLOLIVE INDONESIA
SECOND GENERATION
KUREIJI OLLIE
PRESENT
Crazyになるほど 恋している ZOMBIE
Crazy Zombie in Love
Oh, oh, oh... Zombie zombie...
おやすみのキスを頂戴
Give me a goodnight kiss
Gemes banget sih kagetnya kamu gitu.
Your startled face is so cute~
Padahal ini kan yang kamu nanti-nantikan?
Wasn't this what you were waiting for?
Bisa bicara sama oshi.
To be able to talk to your oshi~
Ngapain itu pencet tombol back?
Hmm, why the frantic button pressing dear?
Jangan-jangan kamu nggak suka Ollie ngomong kayak gini?
Don't tell me you actually dislike this kind of interaction~
Aaa! HP-nya kok dimatiin sih!
Aww why'd you turn off the phone?
Beneran nggak suka ngomong sama Ollie ya?
You really don't want to talk to me huh~
Keseruan baru akan dimulai sekarang.
The fun is just about to begin~
Darling~
存在証明 愛だって 愛だって 吐いたって
Existence proof, it's love, it's love, even if I vomit it out
寝転んゴロンで嫌ん嫌ん プリティプリティ ダイエットDAY
Rolling and rolling, no, no, pretty, pretty, diet day
アイマイ 快楽に 曖昧 一回楽に
I-my pleasure, ambiguous, one time easily
病み悪化してんだって 愛だ 恋だ 何だってんだ
They say the illness is worsening, love, passion, whatever it is
生命線は愛だって 愛だ 投げいたって
Life line is love, it's love, even if I lament
ああでもない こうでもないな 寂し 寂し ナンセンスDAY
Not this, not that, lonely, lonely, nonsense day
いっそ密会 ラフに 節操無い 一解 LOVE ME
Rather, a secret meeting, roughly, without integrity, once, love me
溺れ奴隷 踊れ踊れ 亡霊だ 亡霊だ
A drowning slave, dance, dance, I'm a ghost, I'm a ghost
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない
Nothing, nothing, I have nothing
変われない 変われない 私変われない
Can't change, can't change, I can't change
分からない 分からない 分かる分からない
Don't understand, don't understand, understand or not
はーい 目もと以外は隠して
Yes, hide everything but the eyes
ダダダダ ダリダリ ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da-da, dar-dar, darling, darling
はい冴えない愛情論で おねダーリン
Yes, with a dull love theory, beg, darling
ダダダダ ダリノリ ダーティー & ダーティー
Da-da-da-da, dar-nori, dirty & dirty
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダダ ダーリン
I want to see you impulse, fill it up, da-da, darling
無い無い清純 感情が行ったり来たり
Non-existent purity, emotions going back and forth
無い無い純情 感情で ダダ ダーリン
Non-existent innocence, with emotions, da-da, darling
ダダダダ ダーリン 愛だ 愛だって
Da-da-da-da, darling, it's love, it's love
まぁ寝転んゴロンでニャンニャン 食い意地ダイエットDAY
Well, rolling and rolling, meow meow, gluttonous diet day
もう精一杯で罪 暴論お節介で無理
Already at my limit, it's a crime, reckless argument, meddling, it's impossible
病み垢してんだって 承認 承認 ぜったい
Doing a dark account, approval, approval, definitely
なにもない なにもない 私なにもない
Nothing, nothing, I have nothing
はしたない はしたない 私はしたない
Immodest, immodest, I'm immodest
分からない 分からない 分かる分からない
Don't understand, don't understand, understand or not
はい 自撮りは全部加工して
Yes, process all the selfies
ダダダダ ダリダリ ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da-da, dar-dar, darling, darling
はい絶えない愛情論で 冷めたり
Yes, with a never-ending love theory, getting cold
ダダダダ ダリ無理 ダーティー & ダーティー
Da-da-da-da, dar-muri, dirty & dirty
会いたい衝動 止めてよ ダダ ダーリン
I want to see you impulse, stop it, da-da, darling
踊れ 叫べ 踊れ ルッパッパ
Dance, scream, dance, ru-pa-pa
踊れ 唄え 踊れ ルッパッパ
Dance, sing, dance, ru-pa-pa
もうドッキンドッキ脳 しんどきんどき脳
Already thumping brain, painful thumping brain
はい 素顔は全部失くして
Yes, lose your real face entirely
ダダダダ ダリダリ ダーリン ダーリン
Da-da-da-da, dar-dar, darling, darling
どうしようもない感情論に 笑ったり
Laughing at a hopeless theory of emotion
ダダダダ ダリ脳裏 ダーティー & ダミー
Da-da-da-da, dar-nori, dirty & dummy
会いたい衝動 埋めてよ ダダ ダーリン
I want to see you impulse, fill it up, da-da, darling
無い無い反応 返答を期待したり
Non-existent reaction, expecting a reply
無い無い妄想 感情で ダダ ダーリン
Non-existent delusion, with emotions, da-da, darling
無い無い純情 感情で ダダ ダーリン
Non-existent innocence, with emotions, da-da, darling
ねぇ ダーリン
Hey, darling
けーたいみしてよ
Show me your phone
待ちわびている大通り
On the main street where I've been waiting
目眩しそうな人混み
In the dizzying crowd
くるり回った昼帯
The afternoon belt spun around
立ち止まってる　坊
Standing still, boy
しまい切れてない表情
An expression you couldn't hide
どこ見てるの　坊
Where are you looking, boy?
知らない
I don't know
今なに
What now?
目と目とまった合図
The signal when our eyes met
ロングルーズスリーブ
Long loose sleeves
「あとでね」
"See you later"
黒文字
Black text
隠してもムダね
It's useless to hide it
けーたいみしてよ今から
Show me your phone from now on
けけけ
Ke-ke-ke-
けけけけーたいみしてよ今から
Sh-sh-sh-show me your phone from now on
拒んでるの予想通り
As expected, you're refusing
だって賭けたこの試み
Because I bet on this attempt
くるり回った昼帯
The afternoon belt spun around
立ち止まっていないで
Don't just stand there
怒ったりしないでよ
Please don't get angry
I need チュチュチュ
I need chu chu chu
いらない
I don't need it
苛立ち
Irritation
使い古しの愛も
Even worn-out love
言い訳だらけ
Is full of excuses
画面じゃなくここ見て
Look here, not at the screen
取り上げるからね
I'm taking it away
ねえ今すぐ
Hey, right now
渡しなさい
Hand it over
ねえいいでしょ
Hey, it's fine, right?
けーたいみしてよ
Show me your phone
Oh! You woke up!
Hi, good morning!
Did you have a good sleep?
Oh, here?
This is my room!
What was that?
It looks a bit different?
Ehehe~ I guess you found out.
I... prepared this room just for us.
Because it's a special room!
Yeah... I wanted to make our memory as special as possible.
So I worked really hard, and I prepared the perfect scenery just for us!
I even transported you here while you were still asleep.
I just didn't want you to be tired, is all.
I just love you so much...
...that I want these feelings to properly reach you.
Huh? What's wrong?
I'm not like my usual self?
Ehehe~ You're so silly.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Ah! Wait! Don't go!
Where are you going?
Wow... I can't believe you ran away like that.
But you were so cute when you were so shy!
指切りげんまん ホラでも吹いたら
Pinky swear, if I lie
針でも何でも飲ませていただき
I'll swallow a thousand needles or whatever
Monday
It doesn't matter if it's Sunday
鏡よ鏡よ この世で1番
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who in this world is
変わることのない愛をくれるのはだれ
The one who gives me an unchanging love?
No need to ask 'cause it's my darling
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおさらばするより
Rather than parting ways with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I want you more than three meals a day
あんたとこのままおさらばするよか
Rather than parting ways with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Even so, my heart wavers at times
死んでも治らな 治してみせます Baby
It won't heal even if I die, I'll show you I can fix it, baby
Yeah I ain't nothin' but ya baby
失って初めて気がつくなんて
To only realize once it's lost
そんなダサいこともしたくないのよ
I don't want to do something so lame
Goodbye
Oh Don't you ever say ByeBye
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおさらばするより
Rather than parting ways with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I want you more than three meals a day
あんたとこのままおさらばするよか
Rather than parting ways with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
わたしの最後はあなたがいい
I want you to be my last
あなたとこのままおさらばするより
Rather than parting ways with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
三度の飯よりあんたがいいのよ
I want you more than three meals a day
あんたとこのままおさらばするよか
Rather than parting ways with you like this
死ぬのがいいわ
I'd rather die
それでも時々浮つく My Heart
Even so, my heart wavers at times
そんなダサいのはもういらないのよ ByeBye
I don't need anything that lame anymore, bye-bye
I'll always stick wit ya my baby
ねえアナタには見えない事ばかり
Hey, there's so much you can't see
アタシは見えている事を知らないの？
Don't you know I see it all?
背中につけられた誰かのキスの跡
The mark of someone's kiss left on your back
一人じゃ買う訳の無いそれも
And that thing you'd never buy alone
見て見ぬ振りなら上手
I'm good at pretending not to see
笑っちゃう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's laughable
常時奔放 狂気乱舞
Always self-indulgent, a wild dance of madness
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if I yell, our eyes meet and in one blow
洗脳完了 お上手
Brainwashing complete, well done
愛しているのさ 強く愛しているのさ
I love you, I love you so much
ねえ精神から全身まで
Hey, from my spirit to my whole body
表面から内面まで
From the surface to the inside
脳天から先端まで知りたいの
I want to know it all from top to toe
それから最近聞いた音楽から
And then, from the music you've heard recently
散財した少額まで
To the small change you've spent
完全把握しないと気が済まないの
I won't be satisfied unless I grasp it all completely
とやかく言ったって実際の問題は
No matter what's said, the actual problem is
その眼中アタシ何割くらい担ってるか
What percentage of your sight I occupy
隠してないで
Don't hide it
確信を頂戴
Give me certainty
黙って語らず
Be silent and say nothing
笑っちゃう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's laughable
容姿端麗 耽美甘味
Beautiful features, aesthetic and sweet
身勝手だってシックな素振り
Even if selfish, a chic demeanor
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instant intoxication, the bliss of a woman
愛しちまうのさ されど愛しちまうのさ
I end up loving you, even so I end up loving you
過去を喰らう程にポップなエレジー
A pop elegy that consumes the past
排気から香るラーメン
Ramen smelling from the exhaust
騙し奪われる恋でもいいの
I don't mind a love of deception and theft
だってこの恋はめちゃくちゃ可愛いでしょ？
Because this love is incredibly cute, isn't it?
笑っちゃう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's laughable
常時奔放 狂気乱舞
Always self-indulgent, a wild dance of madness
怒鳴ってたって目が合って一撃
Even if I yell, our eyes meet and in one blow
洗脳完了 お上手
Brainwashing complete, well done
困っちゃう程にキュートなカノジョ
A girlfriend so cute it's troubling
容姿端麗 耽美甘味
Beautiful features, aesthetic and sweet
身勝手だってシックな素振り
Even if selfish, a chic demeanor
瞬時酩酊 女冥利
Instant intoxication, the bliss of a woman
愛していんのさ 強く愛していんのさ
I love you, I love you so much
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl
誘惑される
Being tempted
鼓動に
By the heartbeat
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast of love to the bursting conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't tell you
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing someone
澄んだ君の目を孕んで
Conceiving your clear eyes
Bunny Girl
Lyrics, Music: AKASAKI
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, mark those stylish steps
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue after work
私と、このグラスに
In me, this glass
ヒールに
And these heels
さあ 自分好みに縋って
Now, lean on your own preference
世間に対する気持ち
Your feelings toward the world
私に注いでみない？
Why not pour them into me?
ありがちなラブソングでも
Even in a typical love song
愛が込められてるの
Love is being poured in
それでも汚れるのね
Even so, it gets dirty, doesn't it?
君を見れば分かるの
I can tell by looking at you
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes looking down
無理矢理 剥ごうとはしない
I won't force them open
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べて
So don't make that face, reach out your hand
ほら
See
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
By the heartbeats that tempt me
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast of love to the bursting conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if I can't tell you
恋の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of love, Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って澄んだ君の目を
Piercing someone, conceiving your clear eyes
孕んで
With you
君の愛を知った気で ハイになっていて
Feeling like I knew your love, getting high
感度去っていて 毎度泣いていてさ
Losing sensitivity, crying every time
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That's how it should be, right?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Now, mark those stylish steps
君の顔色今では マシになってきてるから
Because your expression is getting better now
君に委ねるわ Bunny Girl
I'll leave it to you, Bunny Girl
私をあげるわ Bunny Girl
I'll give myself to you, Bunny Girl
誘惑される鼓動に
By the heartbeats that tempt me
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に愛を乾杯
A toast of love to the bursting conflict
伝えられてるはず
You should be able to tell
夜の始まりさ Bunny Girl
It's the beginning of the night, Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って澄んだ君の目を
Piercing someone, conceiving your clear eyes
孕んで
With you
Dah!
Finally found you! I was looking everywhere for you!
You didn't tell me that we were playing hide and seek!
Well, I see you've made it to my neon stage!
How you like it? It's really pretty, right?
I put a lot of effort into it! There's a lot of neons and whatnot!
And um... while you were hiding, I also got a chance to change my clothes!
Don't I look super cute?
Hehe~ Actually there's still a lot more I've prepared for you!
So, I hope we can just end this hide and seek here, yeah?
Huh? No?
Hey, you know... You've been acting kind of weird lately...
You've been acting really weird ever since you got here and...
...I just don't understand!
You've been trying to get my attention...
...by liking my posts and commenting on them.
Isn't this what you wanted?
You... you love me, right?
Don't you want to spend more time with me?
Why are you not accepting my feelings?
You're supposed to be happy, but...
...you're acting so strange.
Eh! Wait! Wait!
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is affecting me, myon.
アハ アハ
Ah-ha, ah-ha
どんだけ泣いたか分かんないや
I don't know how much I've cried.
つら 独りっぽっち
It's hard being all alone.
ぽっかり空いて埋まらないや
There's a gaping hole that won't be filled.
欲しい ラブぴったん
I want a perfect love.
中途半端な出会いじゃ刺さないや
A half-hearted meeting won't pierce me.
やっぱり無理かも ぱたんきゅー
Maybe it's impossible after all, I'm exhausted.
げっそりハートが治らないや
My worn-out heart won't heal.
出してよすぐ処方箋
Write me a prescription right now.
サヨナラのトゲ なんで抜けないの
Why won't this thorn of goodbye come out?
きみの代わりの人型が全然見つからない
I can't find a replacement for you at all.
おー サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ウブの出棺
Oh, Sad Girl Sex, papan, naive coffin departure.
知っててどんな想いだっけな
I knew, but what were those feelings again?
誰かと寝ても寂しさが発火
Even sleeping with someone else, loneliness ignites.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is affecting me, myon.
おー サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ラブの接待
Oh, Sad Girl Sex, papan, entertainment of love.
きっとまた会えるなんてさ
Thinking that we'll surely meet again...
思い出の君に喰い荒らされ子
I'm being devoured by memories of you.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is affecting me, myon.
アハ アハ
Ah-ha, ah-ha
ねえ マンガ返してよ
Hey, give me back my manga.
最新話であのキャラ死んじゃったよ
That character died in the latest chapter.
教えてくれたバンドメンバーが
The band members you told me about...
クスリで捕まっちゃったよ
...got arrested for drugs.
一緒にいたこと消えないや
The time we spent together won't disappear.
全部が二人だった
Everything was the two of us.
きっと君は今誰かといるの
You're probably with someone else now.
あたしだけが課金中
While I'm the only one still paying.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ウブの出棺
Sad Girl Sex, papan, naive coffin departure.
一途辛くてエンバテだわ
Being devoted is hard, I'm exhausted.
上書きしたいどうしてくれるの
I want to overwrite it, what will you do?
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
There's no pity for the gacha of love.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ラブの接待
Sad Girl Sex, papan, entertainment of love.
ちょっとエグすぎないほんとさ
It's a bit too gruesome, honestly.
涙の跡に狂気が走った
Madness ran through the traces of tears.
愛のガチャガチャ天井はない
There's no pity for the gacha of love.
もしもが叶う素敵世界ならば
If this were a wonderful world where "what ifs" come true...
君はさよなら取り下げを検討加速しちゃう
You'd accelerate your consideration of withdrawing the goodbye.
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ウブの出棺
Sad Girl Sex, papan, naive coffin departure.
なんてご機嫌な終わりだろう
What a cheerful ending it would be.
誰かと寝たら埋められるような
Is it the kind of love that can be filled...
レベルの愛だ？そんなんじゃない！
...just by sleeping with someone? It's not like that!
サッドガール・セックス ぱぱん ラブでぺちゃんこ
Sad Girl Sex, papan, crushed by love.
今でも想ってるなわけ
As if I'm still thinking about you.
期待よりの地獄もう戻れないの
A hell beyond expectations, I can't go back.
きみのサ終が効いてんだみょん
Your service termination is affecting me, myon.
アハ アハ
Ah-ha, ah-ha
探せ続行 ダメダメや
Continue the search, it's no good.
揺らせ絶頂 合せ合せわ
Rock the climax, match it, match it.
探せ続行 ダメダメや
Continue the search, it's no good.
君の絶叫 効いてんだみょん
Your scream is affecting me, myon.
檻の中 あたしの愛猫
Inside the cage, my pet cat.
お帰りなさい君ににゃお
Welcome back, "meow" to you.
悪い子ね汚れたお身体で
Such a bad child, with that dirty body.
行きはよいよいで帰りは怖い
Easy to go, but scary to return.
愛を知らない飽き猫さん
You're a bored cat who doesn't know love.
間抜けな今日こそりゃ結構
Today of all days, being stupid is just fine.
睨めっこほらバレバレでございましょ
A staring contest, see, you're clearly exposed.
なんでお仕置き自己嫌悪
Why the punishment? Self-loathing.
君はあたしだけの愛猫だよ
You're my pet cat alone.
だんだん好きになりなさい
Gradually, learn to love me.
...好きになる...
...I'm falling...
...愛して
...love me.
ダン ダン
Boom, boom
好きになる
I'm falling in love
好きになるね
I'm falling in love, aren't I?
愛して
Love me
可愛いね
You're so cute,
首輪つけてニャ 大切に愛でてあげるニャ
wearing a collar, meow. I'll cherish and love you, meow.
檻の中の子猫ちゃん
My little kitten in a cage
愛のダンスさあ踊りましょう
Let's dance the dance of love.
喉鳴らし擦り寄って ほらどうぞ？
Purring and rubbing against me, go ahead.
睨めっこあら甘えん坊さん
A staring contest, oh, what a spoiled one.
そっぽを向いてもそりゃ結構
Even if you look away, that's fine too.
君はあたしだけの愛猫なの
You are my one and only pet cat.
ダン
Boom
好きにして 好きにして 好きにして 愛して
Do as you like, do as you like, love me.
愛して ダン ダン
Love me. Boom, boom
好きになる 好きになる 好きになるね 愛して
I'm falling in love, I'm falling in love, love me.
逃げられやしないの 馬鹿正直な愛が死ぬ
You can't escape. This foolishly honest love will die.
愛おしいんだって 君は愛猫さん
You are so dear to me, my pet cat.
ねぇ、どこにいるの？
(Halooo? Kamu di mana?)
Hello? Where are you?
うぅ～、出てきてよ！
(Ish, keluar dong!)
Ugh, come out!
かくれんぼはもう終わりだと思ってたのに...
(Katanya udahan main petak umpetnya?)
I thought we were done playing hide and seek.
もぉ～、どこに隠れているの？
(Kamu ke mana coba...)
Gosh, where could you be?
早く出てきて！
(Ayo tunjukin dirimu!)
Show yourself!
こんなに探させるなんて、信じられないよ...
(Beneran deh, ngasih kerjaan aja ya kamu...)
Honestly, I can't believe you'd make me look for you like this.
あはは！見つけたよ！
(Ah! Ketemu!)
Ah! Found you!
今度はどこにも行かないでね～！
(Jangan ke mana-mana lagi, ya~!)
Don't go anywhere now, okay?!
言葉引く香る君のそろ髪が
The scent of your trimmed hair, drawing words,
僕の心を躍らせたんです
made my heart skip a beat.
靡くだけ今はそれだけで
Just fluttering, for now just that,
この身屈めますから
I'll bend my body.
Hey Hey Hey Midnight 光線 Darling
Hey, hey, hey, Midnight Beam, Darling
堪え切れぬ欲望に任せて
Leaving it to the uncontrollable desire.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight Beam, Darling
僕に仕える気になったら
If you feel like serving me.
はー 願うは三度の絶頂を
Haaa... I pray for three climaxes
胸の中で至る
reaching within my heart.
今宵も僕らは繁栄のために
Tonight as well, for the sake of prosperity,
矢を放つ
we shoot the arrow.
抗いの呟きとは裏腹に
Contrary to the murmurs of resistance,
身体は嬉しそうに動いたんです
my body moved happily.
この首に鎖をつけるかは
Whether to put a chain on this neck
僕ら次第ですから
is up to us.
真面目ですかね
Are you serious?
淫らですかね
Are you lewd?
Hey Hey Hey Midnight 光線 Darling
Hey, hey, hey, Midnight Beam, Darling
愛と欲に純白を求めて
Seeking purity in love and greed.
Midnight 光線 Darling
Midnight Beam, Darling
僕を拒む気になっても
Even if you feel like rejecting me.
はー 願うは三度の絶頂を
Haaa... I pray for three climaxes
胸の中で至る
reaching within my heart.
零れる涙が飽和して
Overspilling tears saturate,
僕は暇に果てる
I perish in leisure.
その溢れた吐息のせいなんだって
They say it's because of those overflowing sighs.
一体どこからいったって ドキドキなんだって
No matter where it starts from, they say it's heart-pounding.
よろめく恐怖が原因なんだって
They say stumbling fear is the cause.
それでも君ならいいんだって さらに
Even so, if it's you, it's fine, and what's more...
痛めに
With pain
愛を
Love me
もっと吸い愛してよ
Love me and suck it out more
願うは三度の絶頂を
My wish is for three times of climax
胸の中で至る
Reaching it within the heart
零れる涙が飽和して
The overflowing tears are saturated
僕は今に果てる
And now I perish
ねぇあたし知ってるよ 君が独り
Hey, I know that you're alone
知ってるの？ 知ってるよ
Do I know? Yes, I know
ビコンビコン吠えてさ 恋も黙れないんだわ
Howling aloud, love won't stay quiet
正直に言っちゃえよ バレてるんだし
Just say it honestly, since you've been found out
言っちゃえよ？ 効いてんの？
Should you say it? Is it working?
ズツズツ恥ずかし みんな隠しているだけ
Throb, throb, so embarrassing, everyone's just hiding it
むふー
Mufu~
ねぇあたし知ってるよ 君が独り
Hey, I know that you're alone
涙知ってるの？ 知ってるよ
Do I know your tears? Yes, I know
ズンズン凹んださ 弱いヒトから In the night
Thump, thump, feeling down, start with the weak ones In the night
朝が来るまで一緒コース もっと泣いたって
The together-course until morning comes, even if you cry more
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll catch you as many times as it takes
もう我慢しないでいっぱい出してね
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out
Mwah! お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you
慰めさせてシェイクシェイク 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, shake shake, with the talent of love
泣いてくれなきゃ枯れてしまう
If you don't cry for me, I'll wither away
濡れていたいねいいでしょ？
I want to be wet, is that okay?
舐め取って飲み干したいんだってば
I told you, I want to lick it up and drink it all
Mwah! お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you
頼り散らしてシックラブ 何度サイコね
Relying on you, sick love, how many times is it psycho?
沸けてくれなきゃ君の痛い
If you don't pour it out, your pain
感じてたいねいいでしょ？
I want to feel it, is that okay?
吸い取って救いたいんだってば
I told you, I want to suck it out and save you
見たい見たい見たい見たい...君の中
I want to see, want to see... inside of you
見たい見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, want to see...
ねぇあたし知ってるよ 君が独り
Hey, I know that you're alone
悔しがってんの？ 知ってるよ
Are you feeling frustrated? Yes, I know
ズキュンズキュン高まるよ 君を襲うことはやめない
Zukyun, zukyun, it's heightening, I won't stop attacking you
ねぇあたし知ってるよ 君はできる子
Hey, I know that you're a capable one
知ってるよ 辛い時は
I know, when times are tough
弱い位でちょうどいい あたしそれでも好きだよ
Being weak is just fine, I'll still love you anyway
Mwah! お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you
名前を呼ぶよ いつだって参上
I'll call your name, I'll show up anytime
君は一人だ だから歌う
You are alone, so I'll sing
一人じゃないもういいでしょ？
You're not alone, it's fine now, right?
ソロプレイはおしまいなんだってば
I told you, solo play is over
君が病める時も あたしそばにいるわ
When you are sick, I'll be by your side
いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
I'm always watching over you, yes, there's nothing to fear
Ah!
Mwah! お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you
慰めさせてシェイクシェイク 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, shake shake, with the talent of love
泣いてくれなきゃ枯れてしまう
If you don't cry for me, I'll wither away
濡れていたいねいいでしょ？
I want to be wet, is that okay?
舐め取って飲み干したいんだってば
I told you, I want to lick it up and drink it all
Mwah! お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you
頼り散らしてシックラブ 何度サイコね
Relying on you, sick love, how many times is it psycho?
沸けてくれなきゃ君の痛い
If you don't pour it out, your pain
感じてたいねいいでしょ？
I want to feel it, is that okay?
吸い取って救いたいんだってば
I told you, I want to suck it out and save you
ねぇあたし知ってるよ 君が独り
Hey, I know that you're alone
涙知ってるの？ 知ってるよ
Do I know your tears? Yes, I know
ズンズン凹んださ 弱いヒトから In the night
Thump, thump, feeling down, start with the weak ones In the night
朝が来るまで一緒コース もっと泣いたって
The together-course until morning comes, even if you cry more
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll catch you as many times as it takes
もう我慢しないでだしだっだっだっだっ
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out
ふぅ！
Phew!
Akhirnya selesai juga.
縛り終えたよ！
Finally finished tying you up!
Wow! This way you won't be running away anymore~
これで、もう逃げ出したりしないわよね～
Jadi duduk manis aja ya~
いい子にしてじっとしててね～？
So just sit pretty, okay~?
Beneran deh, kamu bikin kerjaan aja ya!
本当に手間をほど焼いちゃったわ！
Seriously, you really made me work for it!
Sampe aku harus cari kamu, kejar kamu~
あなたを捜して追いかけ回しちゃった～
Until I had to look for you, chase you down~
Yaa, yang penting kita sekarang bertemu kembali~
やっとまた一緒にいられて嬉しいよ～
Well, the important thing is we're reunited now~
Sekarang kita bisa nikmatin waktu kita deh berdua~
ついに二人きりで一緒に過ごせるんだー！！
Now we can enjoy our time together,
just the two of us!!
Hey! Attention! Look at me.
おい。こっちを見ろよ。
Nah, gitu dong~
いい子いい子～
There we go~ Good boy/girl~
Karena kamu sudah duduk manis kek gini,
さて、皆さんの注意を引けたところで、
Since you're sitting pretty like this,
now that I have your attention,
waktunya untuk aku perliatin ke kamu hasil kerja aku selama ini!
ついに私がずっと取り組んできたものをお見せできます！
it's time for me to show you what
I've been working on all this time!
Lihat deh!
これを見てください！
Check this out!
今回も誕生日グッズが出ます！
Birthday goods are coming out again this time!
Kali ini juga akan ada merchandise ulang tahun.
There will also be birthday merchandise this time.
Ollie akan perkenalkan satu-satu ya.
Ollie will introduce them one by one.
Yeah, there will also be birthday goods for this year!
So I'll be introducing it to you guys one by one, okay?
はい！じゃあ最初のアイテムはこちら！
Yes! Then the first item is this!
Wah! It's the Wide Rubber Mat! Is this not so cute?
Whether you're working, wherever you're gaming,
you always remember me.
The theme... it kind of looks like a yandere, doesn't it?
But I'm not a yandere, I'm just your girlfriend.
オリーのこと、いつも考えて♡ ワイドラバーマット
Always think of Ollie ♡ Wide Rubber Mat
It's wide, slightly large-sized rubber mat,
recommended for everyday use!
And the illustration is by Hanazono Akira-sensei!
ありがとうございます!
Thank you very much!
Okay, then the next item will be...
こちら!
This one!
Wow! It's a cushion! Isn't this so cute?
Always dream of Ollie ♡ Cushion
クッションだよ！万代...?
It's a cushion! Limited edition...?
So that when you're sleeping, you remember me, you dream of me.
This... it looks so fluffy, so you guys better get it for a good night's sleep!
Alright, and followed by...
こちら!
This one!
It's a ring necklace! Well, it's a ring,
if it doesn't fit your size then you can just wear it as a necklace.
Isn't that really cool?
そう、これはね、指輪。でも、もしサイズが
Yes, this is a ring. But if the size
合っていないなら、ネックレスでも使えるのが超できます！
doesn't fit, you can even use it as a necklace!
オリーのこと、ずっと大事にして♡ リングネックレス
Always treasure Ollie ♡ Ring Necklace
It's so cute! So make sure that when you go out, you wear this,
so that whenever you go grocery shopping, no other girls out there will be hitting on you.
Hi! And then, we also have...
こちら!
This one!
It's a mug! Isn't it so cute? I really like the design!
Even when you're drinking you think of Ollie ♡ Mug
So not only when you're working, or gaming,
or grocery shopping, or sleeping...
but even when you're drinking, you think of me!
And of course, not forgetting...
こちら!
This one!
Situational voices! In three languages!
In Nihongo, in Bahasa Indonesia, and English!
In Japanese, in Indonesian, and English!
Wow, as always, sasuga me!
Wow, as always, expected of me!
Sasuga me!
Expected of me!
Hi! そして最後に、フルセットを購入いただいた方には...
Hi! And finally, for those who purchase the full set...
数量限定で、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
in limited quantities, a handwritten autographed polaroid-style bromide card will be included!
And for those of you guys who buy the full set,
there will be a limited edition postcard with my message and my sign.
Yeah! Jadi bagi yang beli full set-nya itu bakal dapet
Yeah! So for those who buy the full set, you'll get
postcard dari Ollie, ada message, ada tanda tangannya juga.
a postcard from Ollie with a message and signature too.
次は通常版は、箔押し複製サイン入り
Next, for the regular version, a foil-stamped
チェキ風ブロマイドカードがついてきます！
replica autographed polaroid-style bromide card will be included!
For those of you who buy like the normal version,
you guys can also get the postcard with my sign and message.
Yang beli versi biasa juga akan dapet postcard yang ada message dan sign-nya.
Those who buy the regular version will also get a postcard that has a message and signature.
Yap, itu aja... jadinya panjang, ya?
Yep, that's all... it became long, didn't it?
ちょっと長くなっちゃったかな？
Did it get a bit long?
Tapi kamu pasti beli merch Ollie, kan?
But you'll surely buy Ollie's merch, right?
でも、オリーのグッズは買ってくれるよね～？
But you'll buy Ollie's goods, won't you~?
TOPBGT!! やったー!
TOPBGT!! Hooray!
Fluh... ふう...
Phew...
Sebenarnya aku masih mau main sama kamu sih, lebih lama bareng kamu tapi...
Actually, I still want to play with you, spend more time with you, but...
もっと君と一緒に過ごせればいいんだけど...
I wish I could spend more time with you...
tapi udah waktunya kita berpisah... sayangnya waktunya terbatas.
but it's time for us to part... unfortunately the time is limited.
残念ながら時間は限られているんだ...
Unfortunately, time is limited...
Tapi sebelum itu, Ollie masih ada hadiah buat kamu!
But before that, Ollie still has a gift for you!
でも最後にもう一つだけ、あなたに贈りたいものがあるの！
But just one last thing, there's something I want to give to you!
Jadi tolong dengarkan ya... jadi jangan ke mana-mana, oke?
So please listen... so don't go anywhere, okay?
だからちゃんと聞いてね～ どこにも行かないでね！
So listen carefully~ Don't go anywhere!
こちらを見て
Look over here
声を聞いて
Listen to my voice
私を見て
Look at me
私一番で
Make me number one
Loveit?
ゾッとした顔が可愛いね
That horrified look on your face is cute
君のその体が欲しい
I want that body of yours
Loveit? Loveit?
狂い合いたい
I want to go crazy together
可哀想ね 君は悪い子なのね
Poor you, you're a bad child, aren't you?
どの面がお好きで
Which face do you like
左様に
In that way
色目が上手で
You're good at making eyes
頭湧き
With a dizzy head
君に踊らされちゃって
Being danced around by you
アタシは狂う
I'm going crazy
血肉まで
To the flesh and blood
骨の髄まで
To the marrow of the bones
混ぜて空っぽになる愛のパペット
Mixed together, becoming an empty puppet of love
胸が苦しいね
My chest is tight
息が詰まるのね
I'm suffocating, aren't I?
それが恋と教えてあげる
I'll teach you that that's what love is
空ろな声で
With a hollow voice
ほら囁いて
Come on, whisper
いい子ね
Good boy
首輪付けた君はラビット
You're a rabbit with a collar on
イカれちゃったのね
You've gone crazy, haven't you?
恋は盲目
Love is blind
したいよね
You want to do it, don't you?
してあげるわ
I'll do it for you
痛い
It hurts
愚かだね　愚かだね　間抜けな顔をして
How foolish, how foolish, with that silly look on your face.
君は悪い子なの
You are a bad child.
痛いのがお好きで？　産に　惨に
You like it when it hurts? In birth, in misery.
あら　お口はチャックで　何？何？
Oh, zip your mouth shut. What? What?
性に踊らされちゃう　君を喰を
Being danced around by your nature, I'll devour you.
血肉まで　骨の髄まで
Even your flesh and blood, to the marrow of your bones.
しゃぶりつくせば　もう空っぽのパペ
If I suck you dry, you're just an empty puppet.
胸が苦しいね　息が詰まるのね
Your chest feels tight, you're choking up.
それが恋と　教えてあげる
I'll teach you that this is what love is.
君はピエロね　愛を囁いて
You're a clown, whispering love.
人間の形した　君はLove it
In the shape of a human, you're Love it.
イカれちゃっただね　恋は盲目ね
You've gone crazy, haven't you? Love is blind.
したいよね　してあげるわ　祈って
You want to do it, right? I'll do it for you, so pray.
報いようもない汚れ多知に溺れるまで
Until you drown in irredeemable filth.
痛い痛いの飛んでいけ　息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away... until your breath stops.
報いようもない汚れ多知に溺れるまで
Until you drown in irredeemable filth.
痛い痛いの飛んでいけ　息が止まるまで
Pain, pain, go away... until your breath stops.
CAST: hololive Indonesia
Kureiji Ollie (holoro)
Vestia Zeta (holoh3ro)
hololive 4th generation
Amane Kanata
hololive English
Takanashi Kiara (Myth)
HOLOSTARS
Minase Rio (UPROAR!!)
Special guest
Michi Mochievee
Thumbnail & 3D Animation: k3nzoteruya
Tuning, Mix, Mastering: Kururu
合同会社 VESSEL LIFE / um. / 暁 / Koudai / Toshiyuki / sa-sara
VESSEL LIFE LLC / um. / Akatsuki / Koudai / Toshiyuki / sa-sara
ちょめ / SAZA
Chome / SAZA
株式会社音響ハウス / 山田 京也 (Ryoya Yamada)
Sound Inn Studios / Ryoya Yamada
Mchan, ID team
And of course, MY BELOVED ZOMRADES & ZOMILY!! ♡
Thank you so much for coming to watch the 3D Birthday Live!
How was it? Did you feel my love?
Eh, look at that! It's the specially prepared bedroom. Cute, isn't it?
It has a bed, a sofa, Udin... and I don't know if you noticed, but...
...there was a display photo of the people I cherish the most in there.
Did you catch it?
I think the neon stage was really cool too!
You probably spotted a bunch of TVs sitting around.
And well, those are there to help me watch you from afar.
Cool, right?
Ah, but come to think of it, I really did drag you around the stages, huh?
Um, how are you? Do you feel sick? Are you okay?
Ollie was a bit worried, but I think it shouldn't affect you too much since I carried you while you were still sleeping...
Hah? What? No, nothing!
I didn't say anything! Haha! Um...
Speaking of you, you kept running and hiding away from me.
Naughty, naughty! Tsk, tsk!
You always leave comments and like every post I make, so I thought you'd like it if I came to visit.
I didn't think it would actually surprise you that much.
I think maybe it was because you were too surprised when I suddenly appeared in front of you.
Yeah, hmm.
But just so you know, I worked really hard just for you.
Ollie practiced singing, I sang a lot, and changed my outfit so many times!
And I wonder if my feelings reached you? Hehe.
But they obviously did, right?
Also, at the end, I finally managed to catch you.
That's what you hoped for, right?
I mean, because you were running away from me...
...because you love me a lot! Obviously you were expecting it too, right?
Hehe... period!
Anyway, for those of you who are still watching, thank you by the way. I have an announcement!
Ollie will be featured in SO87's song "Love Me Back" with the music video!
It's going to be so cool, so keep an eye out, okay? Mm-hmm!
Ah, it's just so exciting, isn't it?
If you ever feel the need to feel Ollie's love again, then don't hesitate and please come back to watch the 3D Birthday Live again, okay?
Ollie will always be here, waiting for you. Hehe.
Anyways, bye bye! Otsucrazy~!
Crazyになるほど恋しているZOMBIE
Lovin' you to the point I'm CRAZY